chevrolet.co.in 2019-03-17

# Legal Privacy & Statement - Chevrolet India

GM (General Motors India Private Limited & Chevrolet Sales India Private Limited) has tried to make the information here as comprehensive and factual as possible. GM reserve the right, however, to make changes anytime without notice, in prices, colours, materials, equipment, specifications, models and availability. Since some information may have been updated continuously, please check with your GM retailer for complete details.  
Neither GM nor their dealers assumes responsibility for any pricing errors. In the event a vehicle is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information inadvertently, GM or its dealers shall have the right to refuse any orders, which is based on incorrect price/information.

The colours / accessories appearing on your screen are often closed graphical representation and may have slight variations with the actual colour / accessories. The accessories shown may not be a part of the standard equipment.

The precise colour availability with the dealer of your choice is subjected to periodic stock updates.

This Privacy Statement applies to personal information we obtain from and about individuals interacting with GM and its websites, products and services. It does not apply to personal information we obtain in our capacity as an employer.

By submitting material/information to any of our servers (including that of GM affiliates), for example by e-mail, via web pages or through Chevrolet /GM mobile application, you agree to the following terms, in respect to your personal information.

GM will take all steps necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with the current laws. GM uses administrative, technical and physical security to protect the personal information we maintain and to help ensure that it is used according to this Privacy Statement.

You may note that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on GM’s Web site(s), such as chat rooms or bulletin boards, this information may be seen and used by others. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information in these areas.

You may provide us with information about you or your vehicle through a number of sources: GM websites, product and related events, test drive or other incentive applications, surveys, social media platforms, sweepstakes entries and through our customer call centers.

We receive information about you through vehicle sales records provided by your dealer and we may obtain, data obtained from your vehicle’s Event Data Recorder (“EDR”) as described in your owner’s manual (i.e., how various systems in your vehicle operate, the speed and distance of your vehicle). For additional information about EDR data, please see your owner’s manual. We also may obtain information about you and your vehicle from GM affiliates, GM dealers, GM licensees for consumer merchandise, GM credit card bank partners and other sources such as companies that provide lists of potential vehicle purchasers and current owners, if such companies are permitted to share your information with us pursuant to their privacy statements.

The types of information that GM collects about you may include, but are not limited to:

  * contact information (such as name, address, city, state and PIN code, email address and telephone number)
  * vehicle information (such as vehicle identification number (VIN), make, model, model year, selling dealer, servicing dealer, date of purchase and service history)
  * vehicle performance data (such as engine and transmission performance, airbag deployment conditions or crash or near crash information about how a vehicle’s systems performed)
  * demographic information (such as age range, marital status and household composition)
  * non-credit-related marketing profile information (such as when you plan to purchase; the vehicle in which you're interested)
  * relationships you have with GM in addition to the purchase and servicing of your vehicle
  * incentive eligibility verification information  

  * investor information (name, address, phone number and email address)
  * stockholder services information (such as account information)
  * photographs such as those that you may submit for contests or sweepstakes

You give your consent that GM may store your personal information and use it for:

  * to provide products and services
  * to maintain customer relationships
  * to operate GM websites
  * to provide customer and vehicle support and service (such as recall information or warranty service)
  * to provide information and product updates
  * to evaluate vehicle performance and safety as described in the vehicle owner manual
  * for safety and product research purposes
  * to verify eligibility for vehicle purchase or incentive programs
  * for marketing and market research purposes
  * to customize and improve communication content
  * to comply with legal requirements

GM may also disclose this information within its international group (the General Motors group), its subsidiaries, retailers/dealers and their agents for the above purpose, who could be outside India as well and might contact you. You give your consent that the data so provided by you may be transferred to, stored and processed by staff working for GM (including its international group) or one of its suppliers at a destination outside India.  
You make the personal information / any material available knowing that GM may publish/use for commercial, research or other related purpose. You warrant that such information/material is fit for use/publication by GM.

By providing information/material you grant to GM an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute this information or material and you also agree that GM is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purpose.

When you visit one of the GM Web sites, GM may collect and store information about your visit on GM systems. This information may include your personal information, name of your Internet Service Provider (ISP), the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, and the site you visited just before coming to ours. GM may use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving GM sites, for the benefit of GM’s prospective customers.

Some of GM’s Web sites may make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity and to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. So, when you come back to visit GM’s site again, GM can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save your time and provide you with a more meaningful visit.

Similarly, we may also place Web beacons in our emails to measure the effectiveness of our email campaigns by identifying the individuals who open or act upon an email message, when an email message is opened, how many times an email message is forwarded, the type of software, device, operating system and browser used to deliver the email and any URL accessed through our email message.

To measure site activity and provide a better user experience, we may allow our service providers or business partners to compile information from the cookies, Web beacons or other technologies on our websites which may include information about your visit (such as demographic data, browser type, IP address, pages visited, activities conducted on the page and the day and time of your visit). We may also allow third party advertising and personalization partners to use this information to develop personalized content and appropriate advertising based on your visits over time on web sites.

This information may also be used to evaluate our online advertising campaigns or to tailor promotions and other marketing messages to you.

GM has developed certain mobile applications that you may download to your mobile device or vehicle (“GM Applications”). When you download a GM Application, there may be an opportunity for you to provide us with or for us to obtain information about you or your vehicle. Each GM Application may display a separate Privacy Statement that will inform you about how any information shared via the application will be handled and how to decline such use or uninstall the application.

Through the Infotainment system, GM may also offer applications developed by third parties (“3rd Party Application”). When you download a 3rd Party Application to your mobile device or vehicle, the 3rd Party Application may collect information about you in connection with your download or use of that application. GM is not responsible for the collection or use of information by 3rd Party Applications. We recommend that you carefully review the privacy statement of each 3rd Party Application prior to downloading or using them.

GM reserves the right to alter the privacy principles as business needs and applicable legal provisions may require from time to time. Any amendments to these principles will be available on GM Web sites in a timely manner.

The GM information contained herein is designed to be true and accurate. GM reserves the right to change and update the GM information at any time without notice.

**Caution Notice**  
Please be informed to all concerned that GM shall not be responsible for any misrepresentation / internet scam / email scam for promising/advertising to provide job/vacancy in the Chevrolet Sales India Private Limited or General Motors India Private Limited. GMI/CSIPL hire the persons directly through their HR Department.

GM websites may contain links to third-party sites not controlled by GM or covered by this Privacy Statement, such as those belonging to GM dealers, GM licensees, co-branded websites offered in conjunction with a business partner, or independent product review sites. We recommend that you check the Privacy Statement of other sites you visit before providing any personal information.

When you buy or a GM vehicle from a GM dealer, the dealer will share your information with GM as the vehicle manufacturer. Please be aware that each dealer operates as a separate legal entity and you should read the dealer’s privacy statement to ensure that you understand its privacy practices and procedures. Additionally, because the GM dealer often is the first contact with you, the dealer can answer any questions you may have about its privacy practices. While GM encourages its dealers to ensure full compliance with all applicable privacy legislation, GM is not responsible for dealers’ compliance with applicable law.

**Indemnity**  
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless GM, its parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, directors, agents, employees, dealers and suppliers, from any claim, loss, demand, action, or damage, including Attorney's fees, made by any third party due to, arising out of or related to your use of this website, your violation of the terms & conditions, any right of another, your connection to the website.

**Laws And Jurisdiction**  
The interpretation of these terms and conditions shall be construed in accordance with and governed by the laws of India. All disputes, which may arise out of or in connection with the usage of this website, pertaining to your personal information, GM information, this website and/or related information/site shall be exclusively triable by the competent courts having jurisdiction at Gurgaon, Haryana.
